[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1000 - 110",
        "choices": [980, 697, 999, 890],
        "correct": 890
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "400 - 333",
        "choices": [367, 555, 77, 67],
        "correct": 67
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "160 - 22",
        "choices": [60, 140, 122, 138],
        "correct": 138
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "300 - 4",
        "choices": [296, 270, 244, 250],
        "correct": 296
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "200 - 50",
        "choices": [190, 160, 150, 200],
        "correct": 150
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "100 - 10",
        "choices": [90, 80, 20, 88],
        "correct": 90
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "700 - 54",
        "choices": [260, 696, 646, 434],
        "correct": 646
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "440 - 112",
        "choices": [320, 430, 150, 325],
        "correct": 328
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "338 - 337",
        "choices": [4, 3, 2, 1],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "280 - 232",
        "choices": [250, 216, 122, 48],
        "correct": 48
    }
]